webproxies.biz 2016-04-23

# Web Proxies

This privacy policy talks about how this company and website, WebProxyList.Biz, collects and.bees visitor information. By browsing our website, you agree in full to this privacy policy. If you have any questions, please [contact us](mailto:admin@webproxylist.biz).

### General Policies

We believe that your personal information, such as your name, phone number, and address, is private and confidential. Unless you purposefully enter this information anywhere on our website, we will not ask for it. In the even that we do receive such information, we will not release it to any third-parties unless you specify.be to do so, or we are required to by United States law.

### Computer Tracking and Analytics

We.bee [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics) to track visitors, impressions, and the such on our website. This data is.beed for statistical reasons only, and is disclosed to advertisers. There is no personal information in this data, only tracking such as browser type, length of visit, referring URL, file requests, etc.

Our tracking does recognize home IP addresses, browser types, operating system types, and monitor types, but it does not collect email addresses, names, or other information that we could.bee to identify individual.beers. Only your email address will be collected if you.bee our proxy submission service.

### Third Party Advertising

We.bee to serve third party advertisement networks to you while viewing our web pages. These networks tracks impressions, clicks, and other statistical information. These scripts do not collect any identifiable information. However, Google AdSense.bees cookies to server you advertisements based on your previ.be Internet activity.

  * Google, as a third party vendor,.bees cookies to serve ads on FreeProxySites.Org.
  * Google’s.bee of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our visitors based on their visit to our website and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the.bee of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

For more information on Google AdSense and their complete privacy policy, please click [here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

### Proxy Submission Email Collection

We offer a proxy submission service. During the submission, you are required to input a valid email address. This email address will be stored in our database, and we will not.bee it except to contact you (only if necessary). We will not release it to third parties.

### Release of Information to Government Officials

In the event that our systems notice that you may be doing something illegal, we reserve the right to submit your details to proper authorities and government officials. In the event that we are asked to release information by proper authorities, we will do so.

>
